Romina Guimaraens

Career Summary

Romina is a Software Quality Analyst with a passion for the tech industry and a desire to gain experience in different parts of the field. Starting her career in gaming in September 2022, she quickly adapted to the company's frameworks and demonstrated her ability to learn and problem-solve. Her basic knowledge of programming, coupled with her logical thinking skills, has allowed her to contribute positively to her development as a Game Quality Analyst. With a willingness to explore different areas of the tech industry, Romina is excited to bring her skills and enthusiasm to any project she embarks on.

Languages

• Spanish (Native Speaker)

• English (Proficient C2)

Career History

Jam City, Montevideo, Uruguay

Nov. 2023 – Currently

Game Quality Analyst

- Developed test cases and wrote bug reports to track and prioritize issues on the platform Jira adhering to guidelines provided by the client
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure product quality and timely delivery

GLOBANT, Montevideo, Uruguay

Sep. 2022 – Oct. 2023

Game Quality Analyst

- Worked on different components, testing various areas of the game such as AI/Bots and Audio
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure product quality and timely delivery
- Put together organizational systems to speed up her own bug reporting process
- Developed a simple app to speed up the bug reporting process by formatting the informationaccording to the guidelines

Eltonir S.A, Montevideo, Uruguay

Jan. 2019 – Feb. 2021

Administrative/Community Manager/Sales Associate

- Processed e-commerce orders and oversaw delivery
- Managed social media (Facebook, Instagram, and Whatsapp) for two retail stores, providing customer service via direct messaging
- Produced content (photography, reels and stories) for all of the company's social media accounts and kept up engagement by interacting with clients and providing useful information
- Managed to increase sales, both in-store and online by engaging with customers on social media
- Produced video for in-store screens

Education

Holberton School, Montevideo, Uruguay Software Development Foundations

May. 2022 – Mar. 2023

Mar. 2023

Final Project, Holberton School

Front-End Developer & UX/UI Designer

- Created an app called Hay Noche using React as the Front-End Developer and Figma as the UX/UI Designer
- Designed and implemented the user interface, including wireframes, mockups, and prototypes
- Collaborated with team members to develop and test features, identify and fix bugs, and deliver a functional product

Skills

- Programming languages including C, Python, and JavaScript
- Familiarity with game design principles and user experience
- Excellent problem-solving and analytical skills
- Familiarity with game engines such as Unity and Unreal
- Experience with project management tools such as Jira, Testrail, Confluence, and Trello
- Experienced with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, and Adobe After Effects
- Familiarity with React, HTML, CSS, SQL, and Bash Scripting
- Native Spanish speaker with C2 proficiency in English

Contact Information

http://rominaguimaraens.me - rominaguimaraenss@gmail.com - 093701333